[
  {
    "index": 1,
    "Question": "誰も悪くないよ",
    "Answer": "It's nobody's fault.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 2,
    "Question": "それ以上言わないで",
    "Answer": "Don't say any more.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 3,
    "Question": "それは残念",
    "Answer": "That's too bad.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 4,
    "Question": "参加するよ",
    "Answer": "I'm down.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 5,
    "Question": "そうかもな",
    "Answer": "I guess so.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 6,
    "Question": "それヤバい",
    "Answer": "That's wild.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 7,
    "Question": "私は大丈夫",
    "Answer": "Don't worry about me.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 8,
    "Question": "どのみち",
    "Answer": "Either way",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 9,
    "Question": "結構です（断る時）",
    "Answer": "I'm good.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 10,
    "Question": "わかった",
    "Answer": "I got it.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 11,
    "Question": "まじで？",
    "Answer": "For real?",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 12,
    "Question": "すごいやん",
    "Answer": "That's awesome!",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 13,
    "Question": "他にある？",
    "Answer": "Do you have anything else?",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 14,
    "Question": "それいいね",
    "Answer": "Sounds great.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 15,
    "Question": "どうしたの？何か問題でも？",
    "Answer": "What's the matter?",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 16,
    "Question": "いっしょ",
    "Answer": "Same here.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 17,
    "Question": "ちょっと考えていただけ",
    "Answer": "I was just thinking.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 18,
    "Question": "続けて",
    "Answer": "Carry on.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 19,
    "Question": "それな",
    "Answer": "You can say that again.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 20,
    "Question": "元気で",
    "Answer": "Take care.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 21,
    "Question": "わざとじゃない",
    "Answer": "I didn't do it on purpose.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 22,
    "Question": "今回だけだよ",
    "Answer": "Only this time, not next time.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 23,
    "Question": "素晴らしい",
    "Answer": "Terrific!",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 24,
    "Question": "まさかぁ",
    "Answer": "You don't say.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 25,
    "Question": "何が起きた！？",
    "Answer": "What happened!?",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 26,
    "Question": "嘘だ、ありえない",
    "Answer": "No way.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 27,
    "Question": "全くその通り",
    "Answer": "Exactly / Indeed.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 28,
    "Question": "〇〇だったと思う",
    "Answer": "〇〇, I guess.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 29,
    "Question": "話変わるけどさ",
    "Answer": "By the way,",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 30,
    "Question": "今度お礼させて",
    "Answer": "I owe you one.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 31,
    "Question": "そうなんですか？",
    "Answer": "Is that so?",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 32,
    "Question": "それはちょっと、、、",
    "Answer": "I don't know about that.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 33,
    "Question": "ちょっと待って",
    "Answer": "Hang on. / Hold on.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 34,
    "Question": "他には？",
    "Answer": "What else?",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 35,
    "Question": "大変に違いない",
    "Answer": "It must be tough.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 36,
    "Question": "メールちょうだい",
    "Answer": "Text me.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 37,
    "Question": "連絡するね",
    "Answer": "I'll be in touch.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 38,
    "Question": "あってる、正しい",
    "Answer": "That's true.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 39,
    "Question": "多分そう",
    "Answer": "Probably so.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 40,
    "Question": "楽しいに違いない",
    "Answer": "It must be fun.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 41,
    "Question": "頑張ってきたことが報われたね",
    "Answer": "You deserve this.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 42,
    "Question": "マジ？",
    "Answer": "Are you serious?",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 43,
    "Question": "冗談やろ",
    "Answer": "You must be kidding.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 44,
    "Question": "気にしないで",
    "Answer": "Never mind.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 45,
    "Question": "メールするね",
    "Answer": "I'll text you.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 46,
    "Question": "ほんまそれ！",
    "Answer": "Totally.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 47,
    "Question": "それで？",
    "Answer": "And then?",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 48,
    "Question": "なるほどなぁ",
    "Answer": "That makes sense.",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 49,
    "Question": "よかったな",
    "Answer": "Good for you!",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 50,
    "Question": "何が起きてんの！？",
    "Answer": "What's going on!?",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
]